That's Deadly Queen…
I named him myself.
I will eradicate you,
and will sleep soundly tonight.
I warned you. Don't move!
Harvest takes no prisoners!
Such a profuse welcome.
Though crushing
three or four of them
leaves you completely unscathed.
Move another centimeter,
and I'll slice that… whatever that
big artery is in your neck!
Oh, yeah, your carotid!
I'll slash your carotid artery!
I'll hack it to pieces!
My Harvest is invincible!
By the looks of your Stand,
it's the powerful, short-range type.
I'm guessing it's got one,
maybe two meters.
If dying's your goal,
then go ahead and make your move.
Interesting…
So each user is endowed with
a unique ability?
Stand? Hmm… Stand, eh?
I should tell you,
Deadly Queen also has what
you might call a unique ability…
He has something… Grab it!
Huh? A 100-yen coin?
Whatcha gonna do with this?
I thought I'd reveal just
what makes Deadly Queen so unique.
Being that you might
as well already be dead.
Deadly Queen has the power…
to transform anything
it touches into a bomb.
Anything…
Even a 100-yen coin.
Drop the coin, Harvest!
Now, a gentle night of
glorious sleep awaits.
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
A demon's crept into
our everyday life
It's about to take away
something precious
Our peace has already
crumbled long ago
So casually, so nonchalantly
It's taken from us
before we know it
If we want it back,
now's the chance
With the sharpness of
the piercing arrow
The beauty of two souls united
Wherever you go, chase you
Whenever, chase you
I will chase you
Nowhere to escape
Start running, I will chase you
Tomorrow, chase you
My fists will be the one
to show you
Tenacity decides
who will win or lose
So I chase you
EPISODE 22
YOSHIKAGE KIRA JUST
WANTS TO LIVE QUIETLY, PART 2
Have you heard?
Some beauty clinic says
it'll help you find true love.
Huh? Seriously? That's hilarious.
It's true! I heard some
high schooler found success!
So a single blast
wasn't enough to knock him off…
W-What did he do to me? What…
What the…?
What happened to me?!
I told you.
Deadly Queen has the ability to
transform anything
it touches into a bomb.
You see, that's what
I did with this 100-yen coin.
I press the detonator
at my leisure,
and my victim is blown
to smithereens from the inside out.
Though, it seems in
your case, Shigechi,
the blast has partially
imploded your face,
creating a human cocktail of
facial fascia and cerebral tissue.
Before I deliver one final blast,
there's something I must confirm.
This power you refer to
as a "Stand"…
Josuke and Okuyasu wield
the power of the Stand, too, yes?
H-Help me…
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You simply must die.
I can't have a witness
alive and kicking.
Not a single living soul must ever be
able to possess knowledge of
the true Yoshikage Kira.
But you see,
Stand users intrigue me.
I have no doubt
I could find out myself,
but there's no substitute
for the genuine article.
Josuke, Okuyasu…
Who are the others?
How many more are in this town?
What are their powers?
I-I don't know…
Come now, you must know.
Listen, if you refuse
to spill the beans…
I will kill your parents, too.
Wha…
What?
Mommy and Daddy?
Hurry up and spit it out.
Do that,
and I'll leave them alone.
Quit stalling.
I want this between the two of us.
Names are good enough.
Come on, hurry it up.
E-Everyone said so…
There's a murderer in this town,
and they're lookin' for him!
A murderer… They meant you!
You killed Reimi Sugimoto, too!
What? Reimi Sugimoto?!
The shit can still
use his Stand?
Deadly Queen!
That brat…
To think I practically
tore him to pieces…
I-I have to get to Josuke…
Josuke's Shining Diamond…
can fix me…
I have to protect
Mommy and Daddy…
I have to keep Mommy and Daddy
safe from him!
That horrible, rotten man
can't be in the same town
as my mommy and daddy!
HIGH SCHOOL AHEAD
NO MIDDLE SCHOOL STUDENTS
BEYOND THIS POINT
- MIDDLE SCHOOL PRINCIPAL
I have to…
reach Josuke…
Oh, sorry.
Are you okay?
I have to…
What's the matter?
He's a middle schooler.
Something's seriously wrong
with him.
Let's get a teacher…
No, leave him alone.
He's weird.
Let's go.
J-Josuke!
Everyone's looking for me, huh?
Do you mean there's someone
in this town
who knows about
Reimi Sugimoto's murder?
You are aware, no one will ever
be able to track me down…
No one knows
Yoshikage Kira's true colors.
As long as you are no more…
I'm gonna protect
Mommy and Daddy…
Deadly Queen has already
left its mark on the doorknob.
Josuke!
Behold the genius of Deadly Queen.
And with that,
the evidence has been destroyed.
Did someone just call my name?
Yeah, without a doubt.
H-Hey, Josuke, look!
Got… it!
Sh-Shigechi?!
Shigechi!
S-Something's not right, Josuke!
Harvest was hobbling around
spurting blood before disappearing.
That's not how Stands disappear!
Why did just one of 'em
come to see us?
We need to go to
the middle school.
We have to find Shigechi!
Interesting.
Where did I lose that?
Nothing to worry about now.
I do hope my tailor carries
the same button…
No, I don't believe it…
It's happened again.
He's done it again…
Another victim screams
across the skies…
They must have crossed paths.
Shigechi…
There's no question.
This boy has passed.
Shigekiyo and he met,
he killed Shigekiyo.
I have no doubt.
Why they crossed paths,
how he was murdered,
that I cannot tell you.
It was his work.
It's the handiwork of
the man who killed me.
I looked for Shigechi,
but couldn't find him anywhere.
He disappeared in
the five minutes
Okuyasu and I were
separated from him.
Shigechi's books and school supplies
were just as he had left them,
and his parents have filed
a missing person report with the police.
I'd say this is…
Y-You mean…
The culprit is a Stand user?
You guys wouldn't know this,
but Shigechi's Harvest
is practically unbeatable.
This guy managed to kill Shigechi
in five minutes,
and take his body from
the school and hide it somehow.
Jotaro, it's clear we have
a Stand user on our hands,
the rest of us
can't just stand idle.
Josuke.
You found a button, right.
Yeah… Harvest brought it to me.
This is it.
This is Shigechi's dying word.
Harvest may have managed to
pull it off the murderer's clothes.
I'll hold on to this.
I'd like to investigate it further.
Y-You can find the guy
with that run-of-the-mill button?
It's possible.
We might be able to find
the brand and manufacturer
of the clothes it belongs to.
It makes sense…
I-If we're done talking,
I'm gonna go home.
All of this has put me
in a weird mood.
I-I'm really pissed…
Let's go home, Dad.
Okuyasu's just not himself today.
Yeah… Shigechi may've
been an annoying, greedy bastard,
but there was something
undeniably lovable about him.
I can't believe he's gone.
It's the kind of thing
where you don't know whether
you should scream or cry.
It's irritating as all hell.
We all feel that way.
I'm sure Okuyasu feels it worse.
Damn it…
Something horrific was happening,
and I had no idea.
I'll sound the alarm
to all my customers.
Sigh… I can't imagine
he'd pay me a visit,
but for good measure…
Stand users are always
drawn to each other…
Though I hope I never have
the misfortune of meeting him.
So I suppose we must
all step up and act now, huh?
Oh?
That was definitely Josuke…
And Okuyasu, too.
Listen, you won't believe it.
Remember how it was
my birthday last Friday?
Well, that guy I'm seeing
gave me this really shitty ring.
Look at it!
I can't wear this thing.
For now I have to be like,
"Oh, my god I love it!"
I was only going out with him
cause his dad owns some land.
He's a total hick.
It really looks like some toy ring.
How much was it?
I'm guessing like 150,000 yen.
I bet a pawn shop will
give you something for it.
I can't let it ugly up
these beautiful fingers.
Her soul is grotesque,
but her hands and face
are beautiful…
Come my way,
and I'll set that soul right
and show you a glorious time.
Well, gotta go.
See you later.
Okay, bye-bye!
I'm afraid it's good bye for now.
Let's keep this
as painless as possible.
SHIGEKIYO YANGU: DECEASED
STAND: HARVEST
DEADLY QUEEN
Good morning,
and welcome to Morioh Radio.
This is Kai Harada,
your easy listen in'
disc jockey extraordinaire.
Is everyone ready for
a beautiful week?
It's hard to believe,
only three days left in June.
-And once it's July,
- Well, let's dig in.
- You know what that means…
- Oh, that's right.
- That's right. Summer vacation.
- I've got several places
- So what's in store?
- to drop by today,
- I know I can't wait.
- so I'd like you to stay put.
- And now, while the clouds are away,
- We'll dine together tonight when I return.
A fresh jam fitting for this fine day
Thankfully they still
had some of the Parisian specials.
- Talk about lucky!
- Let's get a move on to Yohei Lake.
Wait, Asuka's not here yet.
- What? What's taking her so long?
- It's been four days since that day…
It's been pretty quiet, but…
It doesn't change that a killer
is still lurking somewhere in this town.
When it comes down to it,
the mind sees what it wants to see.
The look of guilt and innocence
is in the eye of the beholder.
Oh… H-Hi, Mr. Jotaro.
Um, did you find anything
out of the ordinary?
Anything about
the murderer's button, or…
No, not quite.
Nothing to speak of yet.
I-I see…
Um, where are you headed?
Nowhere special.
Over there I suppose.
Ah…
Good lord…
Getting the strong, silent type
to chat is like pulling teeth.
Rohan-Sensei's pushiness
is unsettling,
but Jotaro's silence sends me
into a panic.
There's gotta be something
we can talk about… Let's see…
That coat is really terrific,
you know that!
CENTIPEDE SHOES
Looks like we've found
a shoe store.
Huh? Oh! Yes, a shoe store
it certainly is.
Is there something wrong?
WE DO SIMPLE TAILORING
It's a shoe store, but
they also do simple alterations,
like skirt waists and
pant hemming on the side.
There's also an electronics shop
that sells flowers.
Is there something wrong?
I heard all about
the tailors of Morioh,
But I didn't think to ask
about places like this.
Something wrong with this button?
No, if it doesn't ring a bell,
forget it.
I just couldn't remember what
it was originally attached to.
ANIMAL CRACKERS
Hey kid, want an animal cracker?
I save the camels for last,
so everything else is fair game.
Thanks but, I'm fine.
I see.
You know, not only
have I seen that button,
but have a look.
I just finished working on
the suit that button belongs to.
A customer came in yesterday,
asking me to put on
the exact same button.
See? Looks like
the same button to me.
Jotaro!
Good grief.
We found it, Koichi.
Found it?
Oh, n-nothing…
Forget that, what did
this customer look like?
Did you catch a name?
His name?
Well, of course I did.
Do you take me for an idiot?
I remember all of
my customers' names.
Anything less would
be rude to the customer.
Thousands or hundreds of
thousands makes no difference!
Is that so?
Yes! That's amazing!
Could you tell us his name?
Anyway, the jacket
has the order tag.
Of course, I don't need that…
I can remember hundreds
of my customer's names.
It's just faster this way.
Let's see…
KIRA
Now how do you read
this last name?
It must be…
W-What is it?
Please show me.
Um… Um…
Over here.
W-What the?! My hand!
J-Jotaro! L-Look!
Watch it, Koichi!
Don't get any closer!
Hey, I said look over here.
Is that his Stand?!
J-Jotaro!
H-He's here!
He's taking the jacket!
To think someone would go
as far as
to investigate the button
that fell off my jacket…
Did they gaze upon
the name Yoshikage Kira?
Why have I been weighed down
with nothing but adversity lately?
Good grief.
Of course he comes
to get his suit now…
But I shall
make them evaporate
with Deadly Queen's second bomb.
Like that pathetic punk, Shigechi…
It's moving again!
Our evidence!
Wait!
We can't just blindly go after it.
Something's not right about
the way he's pulling the jacket.
This Stand…
Careful… It's gonna blow!
EPISODE 23
HEART ATTACK, PART 1